Let us pray. Heavenly Father, in your word you have given a vision of that holy city to which the nations
of the world, green their glory. Behold and visit we pray that citizens in earth renew
ties with mutual regard which form our civic life send us honest enable leaders to eliminate poverty
prejudice or oppression
that peace may prevail with righteousness and justice
with order and that men, women from different cultures
in differing talents may find one another the fulfillment of their humanity.
And less all schools colleges
universities
they might be lively centers for sound learning new discovery
and the pursuit of wisdom, ignorant that those who teach
in them may find you to be source
of the government. This right here is a program that
state acquires merchandise from federal
Government, excess
it can be any kind
equipment in some cases I understand they might have
something's available for donation others you
had to buy at depreciating cost and wherever
that is this would be for a three year period and we
will renewing. We've had
before I haven't recognized it since
i have been here until
authorized there is a structure to take since an information
authorize the trust man or decide. And on this one
library, fire department
pollution control
electric
Department all of these groups have some items that we want
move because
We don't
need for them at any more
All
of these were purchased by the
departments.
A meeting sometime ago there
was concerns that some
The items might have been transferred to another
department and we did
We just need make sure
Exactly where
money
Was spent for so if
If
Did get
Money through surplus
It would go back
To
Correct
Apartments
And
So
But
With all
Of this
Down
This
was donated. It is all purchased by the departments and I think we are good to go with this list,
so that's why it needs approval of these products on out if you can in-brile
all the websites that there is a beyond.
Guests, dot coms so we can get them to work as people will be at onsite
and guet deals have become very involved they came out took
lot of pictures
They are going help on this website itself
I think it has pretty good service compared
to others that I've looked at.
Thank you, Parker?
Hi!
Good morning
Well resolution M-SU82024 BASHIRAWARPROVING
In a doctor in the Fiscal Year 2425
You tell Ukraine for Boys and Girls Club,
The Water County
And the Community Crisis Center
I have the old agenda
So, this city council has recently approved
This outside organization context
Included in each of those was a detailed credit
so M-SU8
Make a motion we approve
Hi
13 Revised Government of my area
I'm an Air Economic Services
Incorporated for the Episcopal Year 2425
So, when your packet is a Revive
You just approve the M-S contract
But in Your Packages Revised Contract
The three changes are
We added M-SU8
Because of utility credits
They're also going to be assigned around
The contract
Well, this is the M-SU8ment meeting
And other thing
I'm an area chamber of commerce
It's made now so we took that out
And then the spec building
We do not need insurance because they sold this back
So those are very changes
You'll see these again on the council
The still for a thousand percent credit
Up to 11.5
Based On their three year history
That was around in motion approved
Marker
He stepped
The business committee would
Supposed to this agenda
I'm not one thing that say
This morning council member does some pivot and resigned from the board
So we have a lot of net opening now
Just like everybody in on it's 90
We appreciate that
Thank you, thank you. We appreciate Dustin
And his willingness to serve
He though is short
Think he'd be on his control
On this one
He was in board four
So they might have worked for his interest
Or a little bit of an account member
Give me the call or Call it office
We'll reach back up to 15
16. Justin's meeting announcements
17 and German motion
Second
Perfect